老子说了算
跪下干儿子
你就这么跟干爹说话的呀
少他妈占我便宜
我不管你跟我干妈说了什么
今天我非弄死你不可
现在跪下否则
啊你
放开我
陆晨看着自己心爱的女人被绑架
这滋味不好受啊
老三你还真是烂泥扶不上墙啊
既然你自寻死路
就别怪我不客气
你还敢动手打人
赶紧给我跪下磕头认罪
股份我给你
要么拿着股份滚蛋
要么我让你们请假
全家父母启程
别听他废话
我就不信他敢在这动手
陆生你知道我全家有多少资产
就凭你想让我秦家不灭
做梦干儿子
给你机会你不珍惜啊
要么拿着股份给我滚
要么秦家就此不灭
那老子下大的
你说让我全家不灭就不灭
不灭是不是
这是我最后一次给你们机会了
江高管可以动手了
你跟我干妈说什么
I have the final say
Kneel down son
That's how you talk to your godfather
Don't take advantage of me
I don't care what you told my godmother
I have to kill you today
Kneel now or else
Ah you
Let go of me!
Lu Chen watched as his beloved woman was kidnapped
That's not good.
Third, you really can't support the wall with mud?
Since you are seeking death
Don't blame me for being rude
How dare you hit people?
Kneel down and kowtow to me
I'll give you the shares.
Or get out with the shares
Or I'll let you take time off
The whole family leaves.
Don't listen to him
I can't believe he dared to do it here
Lu Sheng, do you know how much wealth my family has?
Just because you want to make my Qin family immortal
Dream son
Give you a chance, don't you cherish it?
Or take the shares and get out of here
Or the Qin family will be immortal
That old man grew up
You said that if my whole family is immortal, it will be immortal
Immortal, right?
This is my last chance to give you guys
Executive Jiang can do it now
What did you tell my godmother?